One.
Một.
Oh, he doesn't look very well.
Ồ, cậu ấy trông không khỏe lắm.
Who?
Ai?
The boy there with his mum.
Cậu bé ở đó với mẹ.
Oh yes, he looks very sad. His name's Tom.
Ồ đúng rồi, cậu ấy trông rất buồn. Cậu ấy tên Tom.
Oh.
Ồ.
Two.
Hai.
So what's her name then? The mum I mean.
Vậy tên cô ấy là gì? Ý mình là mẹ cậu ấy.
She's Sally. She works in the bank.
Cô ấy là Sally. Cô ấy làm việc ở ngân hàng.
Oh yes, she looks very nice in that jacket.
Ồ đúng rồi, cô ấy trông rất đẹp trong chiếc áo khoác đó.
Yes, and nice blonde hair.
Vâng, và tóc vàng đẹp.
Three.
Ba.
Oh, listen to that boy. He's got a terrible cough.
Ồ, nghe cậu bé đó kìa. Cậu ấy ho rất nặng.
Which boy?
Cậu bé nào?
There, look, with the glasses, sitting with his dad.
Kia, nhìn kìa, đeo kính, đang ngồi với bố.
Oh yes, his name's Alex. He wasn't at school yesterday.
Ồ đúng rồi, cậu ấy tên Alex. Cậu ấy không đi học hôm qua.
Four.
Bốn.
Oh, look at that baby on the floor.
Ồ, nhìn em bé trên sàn kìa.
Which one?
Em bé nào?
The one sitting up and reading. Isn't she clever?
Em bé đang ngồi dậy và đọc sách. Bé giỏi quá nhỉ?
Oh yes, her name's Mary. She's Alex's sister.
Ồ đúng rồi, bé tên Mary. Bé là em gái của Alex.
Oh.
Ồ.
Five.
Năm.
And look at those two women.
Và nhìn hai người phụ nữ đó kìa.
Yes, they talk a lot, don't they?
Vâng, họ nói chuyện nhiều quá nhỉ?
I think I know her.
Mình nghĩ mình biết cô ấy.
What, the one with the brown scarf?
Gì, người đeo khăn quàng nâu á?
Yes, and the dog. What's her name again?
Vâng, và con chó. Tên cô ấy là gì nhỉ?
Oh, she's Lucy. And she's sitting with her sister.
Ồ, cô ấy là Lucy. Và cô ấy đang ngồi với chị gái.
Now listen to part one again.
Bây giờ hãy nghe lại phần một.
That is the end of part one.
Đó là phần kết thúc của phần một.